Hi, my name is Jake Brody,
and I'm the family liaison here at New York Congregational Nursing and
Rehabilitation Center.
We are conveniently located in the heart of Flatbush in Brooklyn, New York.
When you enter into our facility,
you'll be greeted by our warm and friendly staff and be welcomed into the cozy
ambiance of our lobby.
We have both private and semi-private options available each with its own
restroom, flat screen TV,
and storage space to make all of our residents feel comfortable and at home
while they're here with us.
We have a newly designed dining room where our residents can come eat, relax,
and enjoy spectacular recreational activities.
We cater to multiple dietary specific needs,
and our kitchen freshly curates a daily menu to keep our residents happy.
Hi, my name is Courtney and I'm the director of nursing here at New York
Congregational Nursing and Rehabilitation Center.
Each unit is designed with the nurses station where you will always be attended
to by one of our caring and smiling staff members.
This is the Rehabilitation Gym.
We are proud to offer therapy modules including physical therapy,
occupational therapy, and speech therapy.
We are very proud of the success of our rehab team whose constant goals are to
make sure your loved one receives the highest quality and consistent care.
We
Also offer a relaxing lounge for our staff and residents to enjoy some peace and
quiet in their spare time.
Thank you for joining us on this virtual tour of New York Congregational Nursing
and Rehabilitation Center.
We look forward to assisting you and your loved ones on their rehabilitative
journey.